beknowledge.com 2010-09-19

# Privacy Policy « Balaji eKnowledge

Personal Information means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, a home or other physical address and an email address or other contact information, whether at work or at home. In general, you can visit Beknowledge.com without telling us who you are or revealing any Personal Information about yourself.

Some of our Web pages utilize “cookies” and other tracking technologies. A “cookie” is a small text file that may be used, for example, to collect information about Web site activity. Some cookies and other technologies may serve to recall Personal Information previously indicated by a Web user. Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them and how to remove them.

You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie, or you may choose to block cookies with your browser. Tracking technologies may record information such as Internet domain and host names; Internet protocol (IP) addresses; browser software and operating system types; clickstream patterns; and dates and times that our site is accessed. Our use of cookies and other tracking technologies allows us to improve our Web site and your Web experience. We may also analyze information that does not contain Personal Information for trends and statistics.

At no point in time will Beknowledge.com working under any of its products and/or services share this information for any purposes whatsoever with anyone outside of the company. In case such a need arises in the future it will be done with full disclosure of how and what data shall be shared. This will not be done without the express consent of the respective individual. All data collected on Beknowledge.com is treated with the utmost care and respect for an individuals right to privacy. We at Beknowledge.com are committed towards creating a transparent and consumer friendly ecosystem of conducting business.

Beknowledge.com occasionally ties up with generic partners for hosting their media content or for strategic purposes. These partners might occasionally be given a privileged status in our ecosystem. Under such a scheme, specific parts of user information might be shared with these partners to provide the user with enhanced services. This will always be kept completely transparent and will not take place without user consent.

This privacy policy is intended to be a generic guideline while using our website Beknowledge.com.Beknowledge.com reserves the right to change certain aspects of this policy as and when it deems fit. The users will always be notified of such changes and will be given an option to opt-out if they disagree with the revised policies.
